<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Services on My New Hugo Site</title><link>https://andyjones789.github.io/mits-website-prototype/services/</link><description>Recent content in Services on My New Hugo Site</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 10:41:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://andyjones789.github.io/mits-website-prototype/services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ai</title><link>https://andyjones789.github.io/mits-website-prototype/services/ai/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 16:23:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andyjones789.github.io/mits-website-prototype/services/ai/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;ve been working with various flavours of AI for a number of years now. Whether that be Speech-to-Text (STT) to understand what a user says, whether that be Text-to-speech (TTS) for a computer to speak to a user, Natural Language Understanding to infer what someone meant by a certain phrase. Or using a Machine Learning algorithm to infer a future result from a dataset. Or Computer Vision to have a machine do the heavy lifting processing images or videos.</description></item><item><title>Desktop</title><link>https://andyjones789.github.io/mits-website-prototype/services/desktop/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 14:59:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andyjones789.github.io/mits-website-prototype/services/desktop/</guid><description>While an “if it’s not broke, don’t fix it” mentality might seem out of date, there’s a lot of truth behind it. People get far too confusing nowadays using technology that isn’t up to par, just because it’s “new” and shiny.
We use Javascript. It’s top-notch, and we’re really good at it.
How do we make your desktop apps look so ace? We use Electron. If you’ve never heard of it before, chances are you’ve heard of things like WhatsApp or Twitch - both of which were created using Electron.</description></item><item><title>Consulting</title><link>https://andyjones789.github.io/mits-website-prototype/services/consulting/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 20:35:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andyjones789.github.io/mits-website-prototype/services/consulting/</guid><description>We’ve been in the technology industry for 15+ years - even though we don’t look a day over 14. In those years, we’ve been lucky enough to build up our own personal technological libraries in our minds. As a result, we have also been able to do everything from educating clients on things like best practices to sharing with them where they should be aiming to reach their goals.
Our custom software consultancy services can also help clients to dig into any existing problems with their technology stack.</description></item><item><title>Ui Ux</title><link>https://andyjones789.github.io/mits-website-prototype/services/ui-ux/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 20:17:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andyjones789.github.io/mits-website-prototype/services/ui-ux/</guid><description>We started the business, we were building technology for users that was perfectly functional. We did the job and it worked at scale but I would not say it was usable, and it was certainly not attractive. The thing we learnt over a number of years is no matter how functional something is, if it&amp;rsquo;s not obvious to the user how to use it or it&amp;rsquo;s not a joy to use, they are not going to get the most out of using it.</description></item><item><title>Mobile</title><link>https://andyjones789.github.io/mits-website-prototype/services/mobile/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 20:15:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andyjones789.github.io/mits-website-prototype/services/mobile/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;ve been playing in the mobile world for 5-6 years. Initially leverage our web skills to build Cordova/PhoneGap apps. Seeing the worse user experience compared to native, we backed off for a year or so. The thing that&amp;rsquo;s always been at our ethos is our clients don&amp;rsquo;t want to build separate iOS and Android apps. They do want the slick user experience that native gives them.
Enter Flutter&amp;hellip;
Truly cross platform but native level user experience.</description></item><item><title>Web</title><link>https://andyjones789.github.io/mits-website-prototype/services/web/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 20:15:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andyjones789.github.io/mits-website-prototype/services/web/</guid><description>This is our bread and butter. We&amp;rsquo;ve been building for the web for years and years. We know it inside out. We build &amp;ldquo;web applications&amp;rdquo;. Think Facebook or where you do your online banking. It&amp;rsquo;s fundamentally different to building websites. Similar technology but usually involves 1000&amp;rsquo;s of hours, rather than 10&amp;rsquo;s or 100&amp;rsquo;s.
Why Web? You may have picked up on the &amp;ldquo;application&amp;rdquo; part of &amp;ldquo;web application&amp;rdquo;. You may wonder how that relates to the sort of application you have on your computer like Word or Excel.</description></item></channel></rss>