<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Previous Work on My New Hugo Site</title><link>https://andyjones789.github.io/mits-website-prototype/previous-work/</link><description>Recent content in Previous Work on My New Hugo Site</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 20:47:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://andyjones789.github.io/mits-website-prototype/previous-work/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Silverline</title><link>https://andyjones789.github.io/mits-website-prototype/previous-work/silverline/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 15:53:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andyjones789.github.io/mits-website-prototype/previous-work/silverline/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Optia</title><link>https://andyjones789.github.io/mits-website-prototype/previous-work/optia/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 15:51:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andyjones789.github.io/mits-website-prototype/previous-work/optia/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Kylar</title><link>https://andyjones789.github.io/mits-website-prototype/previous-work/kylar/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 10:50:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andyjones789.github.io/mits-website-prototype/previous-work/kylar/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Floc</title><link>https://andyjones789.github.io/mits-website-prototype/previous-work/floc/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 20:11:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andyjones789.github.io/mits-website-prototype/previous-work/floc/</guid><description>Background Sports coaching and children’s activities are big business, but most coaches loathe doing admin and chasing payments. It takes hours each week to administer courses and manage fees, yet coaching academies lose substantial income to missed payments, or risk driving away customers when they ask for larger block payments.
The Challenge From 25 years running coaching academies, Stuart Twigg was well aware of the problems of running an efficient, profitable coaching business.</description></item><item><title>Bullhorn</title><link>https://andyjones789.github.io/mits-website-prototype/previous-work/bullhorn/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 20:11:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andyjones789.github.io/mits-website-prototype/previous-work/bullhorn/</guid><description>Bullhorn are the world&amp;rsquo;s largest and most successful Recruitment CRM/ATS (Customer Relationship Management/Applicant Tracking System) so it&amp;rsquo;s no wonder we wanted to work with the best!
We&amp;rsquo;ve been working with Bullhorn for around 7 years, supporting both their and their customer&amp;rsquo;s growth. We offer customisation, confirgation and integrationg third party services. Building portals, mobile apps or enhancing the core Bullhorn product. We also work directly for Bullhorn, both on product and professional services, supporting their meteoric rise in the Recruitment/Staffing space.</description></item><item><title>Grace</title><link>https://andyjones789.github.io/mits-website-prototype/previous-work/grace/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 20:11:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andyjones789.github.io/mits-website-prototype/previous-work/grace/</guid><description>RRadar are a fascinating client - especially given they are a Law firm! Right from the outset, their approach was to change the way law was done. They work on behalf of insurance companies to offer pro-active support to their clients who have taken out a business risk policy. The idea being prevention is always better than a cure. As well as world class telephone and email support for their valued clients, RRadar wanted to add to their already successful &amp;ldquo;station&amp;rdquo; tool, which is a powerful knowledge base.</description></item><item><title>Saeker</title><link>https://andyjones789.github.io/mits-website-prototype/previous-work/saeker/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 20:11:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andyjones789.github.io/mits-website-prototype/previous-work/saeker/</guid><description>Background Saeker are health and safety consultants whose clients include major hotel groups and restaurant brands. Around ten years ago Saeker developed a system in-house which allowed them to create custom health and safety solutions for clients, to keep on top of all the risk assessments, checks, maintenance and record-keeping.
The Challenge Although the system was popular with customers it required substantial time and effort by Saeker’s staff to setup and administer.</description></item><item><title>Originem</title><link>https://andyjones789.github.io/mits-website-prototype/previous-work/originem/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 20:11:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andyjones789.github.io/mits-website-prototype/previous-work/originem/</guid><description>Originem are our ideal type of client - they knew their market and the solution needed, they had &amp;ldquo;made do&amp;rdquo; with off-the-shelf software to prove the market and wanted to build a best in class Software-as-a-Service (SaaS) offering. The software was to be able to run an Umbrella business - a business that pays temporary workers on behalf of the Recruitment agency that found them work.
Originem operated an Umbrella on behalf of their clients through their &amp;ldquo;Cubed&amp;rdquo; offering.</description></item><item><title>Yusen</title><link>https://andyjones789.github.io/mits-website-prototype/previous-work/yusen/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 20:10:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andyjones789.github.io/mits-website-prototype/previous-work/yusen/</guid><description>Yusen Logistics, although not a well known brand outside of their market, are one of the largest logistics firms in the world. They are vital to the supply chains of a host of brands you would use every day.
Most of the Logistics world are focussed on legact technology like IBM iSeries. They had a growing number of requirements to interface with a supplier&amp;rsquo;s and client&amp;rsquo;s systems in more modern ways that were inefficient using the technology they were experienced in.</description></item><item><title>Nlms</title><link>https://andyjones789.github.io/mits-website-prototype/previous-work/nlms/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 20:10:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andyjones789.github.io/mits-website-prototype/previous-work/nlms/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>